

# Aleksandrs Kornijenko

CURRICULUM VITAE

### **Profile**

I am an experienced and hardworking logistics specialist, who have decided to take the challenge and start the carrier in IT field. So, I've completed Software Testing courses and now I am looking forward to start my career in Software Testing.

My best qualities are: high level of responsibility, critical thinking, attention to details, willingness to learn and good team work skills. I am willing to learn new skills and gain more knowledge in testing to put it into work!

#### Courses

Software Testing, SIA Planet of Testing

NOVEMBER 2021 — JANUARY 2022

Java for beginners. From zero till Oracle certificate, Udemy

MAY 2021 — JUNE 2021

Forklift driver license, SIA ITR

MAY 2017 — JUNE 2017

Work safety and health, SIA DARBA VIDE

APRIL 2010

# Work experience

Head of Logistics Department, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

JANUARY 2020 — MAY 2021

Head of Import Department, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

SEPTEMBER 2019 — JANUARY 2020

**Expedition agent, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga** 

FEBRUARY 2017 — SEPTEMBER 2019

Warehouse supervisor, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

SEPTEMBER 2016 — FEBRUARY 2017

Warehouse specialist, SIA ABX Terminal, Riga

AUGUST 2012 — SEPTEMBER 2016

Construction worker, SIA MM Construction, Riga

FEBRUARY 2010 — MARCH 2011

## **Education**

Construction engineer, Riga's Construction College

SEPTEMBER 2008 — SEPTEMBER 2012

Construction site specialist, Riga's Construction College

SEPTEMBER 2005 — SEPTEMBER 2008

Riga's 46. main school

SEPTEMBER 1996 — SEPTEMBER 2005

#### **Details**

Emmas 1, Riga, LV-1015, Latvia +37120352730 cornholio13@inbox.lv

DRIVER LICENSI

B Category driving license

DATE/BIRTH PLACE

21.04.1989 Riga

**Sites** 

LinkedIn

**Skills** 

Attention to details

Teamwork

Communication skills

Critical thinking

Languages

English

Latvian

Russian

**Hobbies and interests** 

Software testing, fishing, basketball, guitar playing